How many people seen the Michael Jackson
movie?
>> [cheering]
>> I love Michael Jackson. I love Michael
Jackson for a reason that most people do
not. I love Michael Jackson because he
is the only black man
to sneak being ignorant past everybody.
Michael Jackson was ignorant as [\h__\h]
but we didn't pay attention cuz he was
doing all this [\h__\h] with the gloves and
then we didn't pay attention to this
nigga's songs. Like example, people
forgot he from Gary, Indiana. That is a
very hood place. Michael Jackson was the
first black man to publicly deny
paternity.
>> [laughter]
>> Billie Jean is not my lover. This is a
girl who thought he was the one, but the
kid was not his son. This was '83.
[\h__\h] was still taking care of they
babies back then, god damn
And he WAS SO SMART, he was giving
subtle signs that we just didn't see the
[\h__\h] cuz he was too smart for his time.
Like this [\h__\h] literally stood at the
bed with her in there, looked down at
this [\h__\h] got in there and lit up and
he disappeared.
There's no better way to tell a [\h__\h]
you not going to be there than actually
disappearing right after you [\h__\h] That
was genius.
>> [laughter]
>> Thriller, everybody loved the video,
nobody paid attention to the song.
>> [laughter]
>> Thriller is a song Michael Jackson made
about taking a woman out to see a scary
movie and afterwards trying to scare her
into letting him spend the night so he
could try to get some [\h__\h] That is
genius.
>> [laughter]
>> Listen to the lyrics. It's close to me
and I, something evil lurking in the
dark. You better come with me, god damn
it.
>> [laughter]
>> And he said plain as day in the in the
end of the song, now is the time for you
and I to cuddle up close together. Yeah.
Ladies, if a man hit you with a yeah
like that, he on [\h__\h]
So, I'mma just spend the night. You
ain't going to try nothing? Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> And he [\h__\h] us up with the video again
because we just didn't understand it. He
was too far ahead of his time. What
happened at the end of the video? She
was scared, he tapped her, she wake up
scared. And he was like, "Come on, I'll
take you home." Right? And what did he
do? He threw us off cuz he had the cat
eyes, right? But it was obvious what he
was on cuz he grabbed her, he said,
"Come on, I'll take you home." WHAT
HAPPENED?
>> [laughter]
>> I SAID THIS [\h__\h] WAS AN EVIL [\h__\h]
GENIUS.
Michael Jackson made real songs with
fake words.
>> [laughter]
>> And is you okay? Can you tell us is you
okay? Heard a sound by the window and he
struck you like a shindo.
The [\h__\h] is a shindo, [\h__\h]
Michael Jackson would beat your ass in
Scrabble, [\h__\h]
This [\h__\h] be spelling [\h__\h] s u m o a e
n. What the [\h__\h] is that, Mike? Shamone.
You don't know what that is like that?
>> [laughter]
>> I know what it means, so I can't even
argue with this [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> Mama say, mama sa, mama coo sa.
And he asked people to help him sing it.
Like he was singing real words.
Mama say, mama sa, mama coo sa. Mama
say, mama sa. Help me say it in a boo
Mama say, mama sa, shook shot, Tupac.
What the [\h__\h] is he talking about?
>> [laughter]
>> I hate I hate that Netflix put that
[\h__\h] ass movie up.
That pedophile [\h__\h] I [\h__\h] anybody who
thought he did it. I knew
when I seen him on 20/20 that he was
innocent. And I'm going to tell you how.
When he did that interview
with that white guy
and he climbed that tree in penny
loafers, I said he didn't do that [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> That [\h__\h] ain't rape no kids. He is a
kid. Who the [\h__\h] at 37 can climb a tree
in some [\h__\h] penny loafers?
And he looked so disappointed that the
guy didn't follow him. You remember he
looked down he was like, "Come on." Dude
was like,
"No."
He was like, "You don't climb trees?"
Dude was like, "Hell no." He was like,
"That's too bad." I [clears throat] was
like, "That [\h__\h] innocent, bro."
>> [laughter]
>> That [\h__\h] ain't did that [\h__\h]
Black men don't get to die clean. This
is just what it is. They find some [\h__\h]
wrong with everybody.
Prince, they tried to say he had AIDS. I
said, "God damn, Prince?
Why we can't die clean?"
Prince didn't Listen, and all them
conspiracy theories, I'mma say this and
I'mma go.
Prince died cuz his hips hurt. End of
story.
He took pills
because his hips hurt. This [\h__\h] wore
high heels for 40 years.
A man hip is not designed to do this
[\h__\h] for 40 years. It gave out.
There's no conspiracy. It wasn't because
he he tried to buy his music back. His
hip blew out. That's it.
Black people always look for the
conspiracy. Bill Cosby didn't do it
either.
He just made promises he didn't keep.
He was like, "Hey, if you suck my dick,
you can be in Ghost Dad, too.
>> [laughter]